{
    "id": "e17eeaba0c474487a90ba7d8fbcfbf36",
    "title": "Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is under the ………………….. that she is a genius.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "illusion",
                "allusion",
                "delusion"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "2) You had better …………………… your ways.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "mend",
                "to mend",
                "mended"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "His mother said, ‘He has gone to the market.’ It is the direct form of:",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "His mother asked me that he has gone to the market.",
                "His mother told me that he has gone to the market.",
                "His mother told me that he had gone to the market."
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Teacher asked me whether I enjoyed the vacation. This is the indirect form of:",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Teacher said me, ‘Do you enjoy the vacation?’",
                "Teacher asked, ‘Did you enjoy the vacation?’",
                "Teacher said to me, ‘Did you enjoy the vacation?’"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ………………….. unanimous decision.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Discretion is the …………………. part of valor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "best",
                "better",
                "good"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. the Taj Mahal last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "had seen",
                "was seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys behaved rudely. Ask question so that rudely is the answer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Who behaved rudely?",
                "How did the boys behave?",
                "How do the boys behave?"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Although he is old, ………………… .. Complete the following sentence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he is quite healthy",
                "but he is quite healthy",
                "yet he is quite healthy"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "God helps those who help …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "themself",
                "themselves",
                "himself"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}